// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the father of C language?",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Steve jobs",
      "James Gosling",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
    answer: "int $main",
    options: [
      "int number",
      "float rate",
      "int variable_count",
      "int $main"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "All keywords in C are__",
    answer: "LowerCase letters",
    options: [
      "LowerCase letters",
      "UpperCase letters",
      "CamelCase letters",
      "None of the above mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is valid C expression?",
    answer: "int my_num=100000;",
    options: [
      "int my_num=100,000;",
      "int my_num=100000;",
      "int my num=1000;",
      "int $my_num=10000;"
    ]
  },
    
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable name in C?",
    answer: "volatile",
    options: [
      "volatile",
      "true",
      "friend",
      "export"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is short int in C programming?",
    answer: "Short is the qualifier and int is the basic data type",
    options: [
      "The basic data type of C",
      "Qualifier",
      "Short is the qualifier and int is the basic data type",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which keyword is used to prevent any changes in the variable within a C program?",
    answer: "const",
    options: [
      "immutable",
      "mutable",
      "const",
      "volatile"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is an example of iteration in C?",
    answer: "all of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "for",
      "while",
      "do-while",
      "all of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Functions can return enumeration constants in C?",
    answer: "true",
    options: [
      "true",
      "false",
      "depends on the compiler",
      "depends on the standard"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The C-preprocessors are specified with__symbol?",
    answer: "#",
    options: [
      "#",
      "$",
      "double quotes",
      "&"
    ]
  },
  
  

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];